[{"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "Is this injury consistent with Mr. Zimmerman's head having impacted a sidewalk?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Is the injury you see in this exhibit consistent with having been punched in the nose?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "That's correct, sir.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Now, Doctor, you're not saying -- you're not testifying here as to who started what led up to the death of Trayvon Martin?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "That's correct, sir.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "You can't say into that, correct?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "I MAIO: That's correct, sir.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "In fact, you can't testify as to who threw the first punch?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "That's correct, sir.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "In fact, you can't really testify whether there was a first punch thrown?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "This is the nitty-gritty.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "What happens next procedurally in the trial?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Ashleigh Banfield, thank you very much, indeed.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Do we think we can go all the way?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Well, this is an epic battle and at its heart, Piers, is whether or not they're going to put the dead, young man, the victim on trial here, and the defense wants to take text messages and Facebook posts that make Trayvon Martin look bad, that indicate that maybe he was talking about fighting or talking about firearms.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "What is going on, do you think?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Well, she's an African-American lady who testified via Skype and I think the unspoken message from the defense was look, George Zimmerman has an African-American neighbor with whom he is friendly.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "But how significant do you think was her testimony?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Well, Judge Alex, this is getting down to the real nitty-gritty now, isn't it?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "This animation video, I mean, it's pure propaganda, isn't it?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "I thought it was devastating.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Take it in totality, what did you think of it?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "That's a good way to start because if you're the attacker then obviously you have a lot more to do in order to be able to claim self-defense.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Is that not the big question because to win a successful self-defense argument, doesn't George Zimmerman have to establish in the jury's eyes that he was attacked first?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "At the end, that's all that matters.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Is that all that matters in the end?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think that the state has proven a case of second-degree murder or, frankly, even come close to it.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "As we approach the absolute final moments now of the defense case, what is your thought about where this case is going?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "I'm sorry, of the defendant, I apologize, where he's got blood there, right?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "I put a hand over that, right?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Blood.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "What do you expect my hand to have on it?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Well, I have no problem with there being no DNA from a gun because it was handled and probably not handled the best way.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Why would there be no DNA whatsoever on Trayvon Martin that related to the gun or to George Zimmerman?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Well, all you have is the evidence that you have.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "It just doesn't really fly, is it?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "I don't -- he's cutting out.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "But in the end, you are still left, aren't you, with unanswered questions, and the big question for me and I think many people is, if there are so many unanswered questions, will the jury be able to let him just walk free?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "At that point they weren't witnesses, they were parents.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Was there any conversation with law enforcement before that as to how to accomplish or finding the tapes for these witnesses before it happened?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "The decision was made to make them public.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "The mayor just decided on your own as to how they would be played?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Absolutely and I think part of it was a political response to, you know, what was beginning to be civic unrest.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "I mean, it was a curious set of events, wasn't it, after Trayvon Martin died?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, if so, it really was just a response to what -- how this whole thing started.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Shawn Holley, I mean, have politics taken over from law enforcement here?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Let me first say that I don't concede that that hypothetical is not also counter functional.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "And we assume that he was stunned, if that is all right, was he justified given he's legally allowed to carry a firearm, and he's stunned, he's incoherent, is he justified in self-defense in using that weapons?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know that there will be any ramifications.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What will the ramifications be of this case, do you think?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "We wouldn't be having this conversation, would we?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "I don't know what the hell --", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "And you know, all those times the two of you asked me why I'm a Republican as if that's something that needs an explanation?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, having to do all the homework on -- like for the Zimmerman trial, like you just did, I mean, you really have to become an expert on whatever the issue is of the day.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "What have you learned about perhaps the difficulties of the job that I do and other news anchors do from doing now two seasons of \"Newsroom\"?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "I agree.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Because it has in a strange way, it's gripped many Americans, others think, you know, that the networks are going to be gone this and in the end it's just another murder case or many other in America every day, but I think it says more about America, but what do you think?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Yes, well, I'm one of the guys that goes back to the Second Amendment and just goes, you know what, it was a different time and now we're into the Sandy Hooks and the -- you know, all of that and whatever happened between George Zimmerman and Trayvon Martin that night, only they know.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "What about self-defense, guns, the right of an American to carry one in the first place in that situation and to use it, and potentially he may well walk away a freeman?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "I -- well, I think it's at the voting booth.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "How does America come through this and be better?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I think Aaron did a really great job of -- in season one.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "One of the big story lines coming up that you think will resonate most?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Well, after I threw the tantrum?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Please tell me you threw a tantrum.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "After that?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "ANIELS: I go back to \"Purple Rose in Cairo\" with Woody Allen.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "How did you feel as an actor in that situation after putting all that work in?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "I couldn't believe it.", "docId": "130709pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard that he died at 51?", "qSentId": 553}]